{
    "subject": "Therese_of_Saxe-Hildburghausen",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Ludwig_I_of_Bavaria",
    "human_readable": "Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen is married to Ludwig I of Bavaria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9637348055839539,
            "question": "Who was Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9486598372459412,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen and Ludwig I of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8958852291107178,
            "question": "Was Ludwig I of Bavaria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8956165313720703,
            "question": "What is the name of Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7008693814277649,
            "question": "Who was Ludwig I of Bavaria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6015494465827942,
            "question": "Was Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen a queen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5729107856750488,
            "question": "To which royal family did Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48644936084747314,
            "question": "Who was the Queen Consort of Bavaria during Ludwig I's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4354342520236969,
            "question": "In what country did Ludwig I of Bavaria reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4000352621078491,
            "question": "What is the name of the kingdom ruled by Ludwig I of Bavaria?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen is married to Ludwig I of Bavaria.",
            "html": "yago_30994_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what country did Ludwig I of Bavaria reign?",
            "html": "yago_30994_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was the Queen Consort of Bavaria during Ludwig I's reign?",
            "html": "yago_30994_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family did Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen belong?",
            "html": "yago_30994_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30994_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen was the consort and wife of King Ludwig I of Bavaria. For example, one document states, \"Therese of Saxe-Hildburghausen (Therese Charlotte Luise; 8 July 1792 \u2013 26 October 1854) was the consort of King Ludwig I of Bavaria.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}